Ariadna Vanegas-Rubio

Junior Front-End Developer

EXPERIENCE

MakeInspires | Mamaroneck, New York | February 2022 – Present *STEM Instructor*

- Implemented and curated curricula to enhance learning and retention of coding techniques and methodologies by 20%
- Facilitated hands-on coding exercises and projects, allowing students to apply their knowledge and develop practical skills in front-end development
- Prepared and delivered grade-appropriate presentations on STEM concepts, guiding students through interactive activities that fostered a fun and encouraging learning environment

Mioym | Rye Brook, New York | March 2023 – May 2023 *Software Engineer Intern*

- Developed and implemented custom web scraping scripts using JavaScript, Node.js, and popular libraries/frameworks such as Puppeteer, Cheerio, and Axios, resulting in a significant increase of 23% in leads and generating over 6,000+ leads
- Utilized Postman to write and execute HTTP requests, handle responses, and validate API endpoints for seamless data retrieval
- Collaborated with team members to optimize and fine-tune scraping scripts for improved performance, efficiency, and scalability

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | Remote | August 2022 – December 2022

Training Participant

- Participated in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learned and deployed the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- o Implemented basic unit tests and deployed the application to Docker

eTeam Inc | Bronx, New York | July 2021 – August 2022 *Patient Care Associate*

- Maintained 700+ client records and utilized CRM to analyze patient data, thereby improving the delivery of medical care by 30%
- Communicated and collaborated with Charge Nurse and Nurse teams to provide care for patients via messaging system through an electronic health record system
- Cooperated with patients to quickly identify problems regarding appointments and medication and developed solutions

EDUCATION

Florida International University | Sweetwater, Florida B.S. in Recreation & Sport Management

Generation USA | Remote | December 2022 Full Stack Java Developer Certification (347)340-5215 ariadna.vanegas@gmail.com Bronx, New York linkedin.com/in/avrubio/ github.com/avrubio avrubio.dev

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate, technically proficient, detailoriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me to further enhance my skills in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools JavaScript Certification November 2022

o HTML

 SOLID OOP Principles

JavaScriptJava

o CSS

Dependencies
Injection
Unit Testing

SQLREST APIs

(JUnit, Mockito)

o Spring Data JPA

Node.jsSpringBoot

Spring Security

SpringBotBootstrap

(JWT)

PROJECTS

Bao Sing Se - Creator, Developer

- Developed front-end with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Vanilla JS.
- Created Mobile Responsive User Experience with CSS Grids that allowed the user to view on any device screen size
- Implemented a fully working web application with the following layers: Persistence: MySQL Database. Backend: REST API with Java and Spring Boot.

OmniFood - Developer

- Developed front-end user experience using vanilla JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Allowed users to have a customized experience based on meal plans selected